A Guide to the Harry Flood Byrd, Sr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series IV: Miscellaneous Topics
  - F. Speeches and Statements
    - 2. Harry Flood Byrd's Speeches
      - Senate - Remarks on Meat Imports, 1964 July 1 (Box Box 394)
      - Civic Center Campaign Committee, Winchester, Virginia, 1964 July 16 (Box Box 394)
      - Reunion of Descendants and Friends of Germanna Colonists, Siegen Forest, Virginia, 1964 July 19 (Box Box 394)
      - Annual Meeting of Commonwealth's Attorneys, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 1964 July 25 (Box Box 394)
      - Reference in the Record to Senator Byrd's remarks on Prince Edward County, 1964 July 28 (Box Box 394)
      - Senate - Remarks on Meat Imports, 1964 August 11 (Box Box 394)
      - Orchard Picnic, 42nd one, Berryville, Va., 1964 August 15 (Box Box 394)
      - Senate - Remarks on H.R.1839, meat imports, 1964 August 18 (Box Box 395)
      - Senate - Remarks in reporting H.R.4844, H.R.5739 and H.R.10467, 1964 August 21 (Box Box 395)
      - Amendment offered by Senator Thurmond, Byrd et. al. on reapportionment, 1964 September 15 (Box Box 395)
      - Senate - Remarks on the retirement of Jerry O'Leary, 1964 September 30 (Box Box 395)
      - Reference to Senator Byrd by Senator Anderson on H.R. 12253, Tariff Schedules, 1964 September 30 (Box Box 395)
      - Godfrey Field, Leesburg Municipal Airport, 1964 October 10 (Box Box 395)
      - Blackstone Presbyterian Church, Blackstone, Virginia. (Speech read), 1964 October 16 (Box Box 395)
      - Yorktown Day Ceremony, Yorktown, Virginia, 1964 October 19 (Box Box 395)
      - Wilson Birthplace, Staunton, Virginia, 1964 October 29 (Box Box 395)
      - Dinner given in Senator's honor by Hiram Lodge, Winchester, Virginia, 1964 October 31 (Box Box 395)
      - Dedication of Beaver Creek Watershed Project, Crozet, Virginia, 1964 November 10 (Box Box 395)
      - Federal Tax Reduction Bill, [1964] (Box Box 395)
      - Senate - Remarks on submitting S. Con. Res. 12 Provision for one General Authorization Act for each fiscal year, 1965 January 26 (Box Box 395)
      - Senate - Remarks on our Gold and Fiscal weakness, 1965 January 28 (Box Box 395)
      - Remarks on the nomination of Mr. Raymond Guest to be Ambassador to Ireland, 1965 March 9 (Box Box 395)
      - Senate - Remarks on the 100th Anniversary, Appomattox, Virginia, 1965 March 25 (Box Box 395)
      - Remarks reporting the nomination of Henry H. Fowler to be Secretary of Treasury, 1965 March 25 (Box Box 395)
      - 30th Anniversary of the Soil Conservation Program, 1965 April 27 (Box Box 395)
      - Senate - Remarks on S.701, Coffee Agreement, 1965 May 13 (Box Box 395)
      - Accepting New Market Award at V.M.I., Lexington, Virginia, 1965 May 15 (Box Box 395)
      - Order Fraternal Americans, Alexandria, Va., 1965 May 17 (Box Box 395)
      - Senate - Tribute to Senator Richard B. Russell, 1965 May 24 (Box Box 395)
      - Senate - Remarks on Amendments to the Social Security Bill, 1965 May 25 (Box Box 395)
      - Senate - Remarks on The Character of Lee, 1965 May 25 (Box Box 395)
      - Senate - Remarks on Utilization of U. S. Foreign Currency Balances, 1965 June 1 (Box Box 395)
      - Senate - Remarks on increasing the public debt, 1965 June 16 (Box Box 395)
      - Individual Views - Medicare, 1965 July 7 (Box Box 395)
      - Commissioners of the Revenue Association of Virginia, Richmond, Virginia, 1965 November 4 (Box Box 395)
      - Notes on Miscellaneous Speeches, n.d. (Box Box 396)
      - Miscellaneous Speeches, ca: 26 items, n.d. (Box Box 396)
      - Miscellaneous Speeches, ca: 20 items, n.d. (Box Box 396)
      - Miscellaneous Speeches, ca: 18 items, n.d. (Box Box 396)
      - Concurrent Resolution - Single Appropriation Bill, ca: 2 items, n.d. (Box Box 396)
      - Joint Resolution, ca: 2 items, n.d. (Box Box 396)
    - 3. Harry Flood Byrd's Public Statements and Press Releases
      - Virginia Road Problem, 1923 January 6 (Box Box 397)
      - Presidential Campaign, 1924 (Box Box 397)
      - Campaign Statements, 1925 (Box Box 397)
      - Program of Progress, Richmond, Virginia, 1927 December 7 (Box Box 397)
      - Tax Segregation - Tax Situation in Virginia, 1927 (Box Box 397)
      - Tax Segregation - Repeal of the State Tax on Land and Personal Property, 1927 (Box Box 397)
      - Virginia Progress, Richmond, 1928 June 6 (Box Box 397)
      - Virginia Financial Plan Now Is Model For Nation, 1929 (Box Box 397)
      - Comment on Governor Pollard's Message to 1932 General Assembly, 1932 January (Box Box 397)
      - Organization, Presidential Campaign, 1932 July 4 (Box Box 397)
      - Byrd Road Plan, 1932 (Box Box 397)
      - As Chairman of National Committee Finance Group. Presidential Campaign Fund Solicitation, 1932 (Box Box 397)
      - 18th. Amendment, 1933 April 8 (Box Box 397)
      - Trade Barriers, 1933 April 27 (Box Box 397)
      - "block Roosevelt", 1933 June 10 (Box Box 397)
      - Governor Stuart, 1933 July 25 (Box Box 397)
      - 18th. Amendment, 1933 September 19 (Box Box 397)
      - Purchase of cattle, 1933 October 17 (Box Box 397)
      - Skyline road, 1933 October 17 (Box Box 397)
      - 18th. Amendment, 1933 (Box Box 397)
      - Beer Bill, 1933 (Box Box 397)
      - In regard to positions in Washington, 1933 (Box Box 397)
      - Farmers' Troubles, 1933 (Box Box 397)
      - On the address of the President, 1934 January 3 (Box Box 397)
      - Cattle, A Basic Commodity, Washington, D. C., 1934 January 11 (Box Box 397)
      - A. B. C. Board, 1934 March 28 (Box Box 397)
      - A. B. C. Board, 1934 April 4 (Box Box 397)
      - Trade Agreements, 1934 May 21 (Box Box 397)
      - Professor Tugwell, 1934 June 11 (Box Box 397)
      - A. A. A., 1934 June (Box Box 397)
      - A. A. A., 1934 November 1 (Box Box 397)
      - Old Age Pensions, 1935 January 31 (Box Box 397)
      - Virginia's share of the public debt, 1935 February 22 (Box Box 397)
      - Public Works, 1935 February 26 (Box Box 397)
      - Wagner Pension and Social Security Bill, 1935 February (Box Box 397)
      - Government Finances, 1935 March 12 (Box Box 397)
      - Thanks Kingfish for compliment, 1935 March 16 (Box Box 397)
      - Labor, 1935 May 24 (Box Box 397)
      - Boy Scouts, 1935 May 31 (Box Box 397)
      - Veteran's Bonus, 1935 May (Box Box 397)
      - Wheeler-Rayburn Bill, 1935 June 18 (Box Box 397)
      - Tax Exempt Bonds, 1935 June 21 (Box Box 397)
      - A. A. A, 1935 July 11 (Box Box 397)
      - Farm-to-Markets Roads, 1935 July 23 (Box Box 397)
      - Public Utilities, [1935?] (Box Box 397)
      - Roanoke Times, 1936 January 11 (Box Box 397)
      - Reorganization, 1936 March 12 (Box Box 397)
      - Corporation Taxes, 1936 May 12 (Box Box 397)
      - Economy in Government, 1936 May 29 (Box Box 397)
      - Norfolk Convention, 1936 June 16 (Box Box 397)
      - Wildlife Federation, 1936 June 17 (Box Box 397)
      - Taxes, 1936 June 19 (Box Box 397)
      - Reorganization, 1936 July 1 (Box Box 397)
      - Tax on Bonds, 1936 August 17 (Box Box 397)
      - The Constitution, 1936 September 17 (Box Box 397)
      - Reorganization, 1936 December 31 (Box Box 397)
      - Interview with Mr. Essary, 1937 January 1 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization, 1937 January 12 (Box Box 398)
      - Brookings Report, Chapter 1, 1937 January 14 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization, 1937 March 28 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization, 1937 April 19 (Box Box 398)
      - Economy in Government, 1937 April 20 (Box Box 398)
      - Governor Pollard, 1937 April 28 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization, 1937 May 6 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization, 1937 May 17 (Box Box 398)
      - Virginia Homestead Projects, 1937 May 24 (Box Box 398)
      - Virginia Homestead Projects, 1937 May 29 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization of the Federal Government, 1937 May 31 (Box Box 398)
      - Tax Exempt Securities and Salaries, 1937 June 1 (Box Box 398)
      - Brookings Report, Chapter 9, 1937 June 7 (Box Box 398)
      - In connection with Washington-Merry-Go-Round, 1937 June 9 (Box Box 398)
      - Campaign Financing, 1937 June 10 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization, 1937 June 14 (Box Box 398)
      - Tax Exempt Securities, 1937 June 28 (Box Box 398)
      - Virginia Homestead Projects, 1937 July 5 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization, 1937 July 10 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization of the Federal Government, 1937 July 23 (Box Box 398)
      - Delivery of mails during strikes at Cleveland, Ohio, 1937 July 31 (Box Box 398)
      - Virginia Homestead Projects, 1937 August 2 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization, 1937 August 12 (Box Box 398)
      - Resettlement, 1937 September 2 (Box Box 398)
      - Tax exempt salaries and securities, 1937 September (Box Box 398)
      - U. S. News - "How To Restore Confidence", 1937 October 21 (Box Box 398)
      - Questions on International Relations, 1937 October (Box Box 398)
      - Virginia Tobacco allotment under the Federal Farm Bill, 1937 December 11 (Box Box 398)
      - Soil Conservation, 1937 December 16 (Box Box 398)
      - Government Reorganization, 1937 December 27 (Box Box 398)
      - The National Debt, 1937 (Box Box 398)
      - Resettlement Administration, 1937 (Box Box 398)
      - Federal Appropriations for Roads, etc., 1938 January 2 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization, 1938 January 16 (Box Box 398)
      - Radio-Grange. Reorganization, 1938 January 22 (Box Box 398)
      - Air Mail service for Norfolk, 1938 February 16 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization, 1938 March 7 (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization - l0% reduction, 1938 March 18 (Box Box 398)
      - Pump Priming, 1938 April 11 (Box Box 398)
      - Taxation of government pay roll salaries, 1938 April 18 (Box Box 398)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1938 May 3 (Box Box 398)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1938 May 4 (Box Box 398)
      - Deficiency Bill - Construction of two additional battleships at Norfolk Yard, 1938 May 9 (Box Box 398)
      - Virginia's Proportion of Federal Grants, 1938 May 16 (Box Box 398)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1938 June 14 (Box Box 398)
      - Kerr-Smith Tobacco Taxes, 1938 June 29 (Box Box 398)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1938 June 30 (Box Box 398)
      - Senator Byrd's Tobacco Res. - S. 291, 1938 June (Box Box 398)
      - Reorganization. Paul Mallon Column, 1938 July 15 (Box Box 398)
      - Federal Debt. (A. P.), 1938 August (Box Box 398)
      - Regional Laboratories, 1938 September 7 (Box Box 398)
      - Research Laboratories, 1938 September 15 (Box Box 398)
      - Exportation of tobacco seed and plants, 1938 (Box Box 398)
      - Reply to Eccles' letter, 1939 January 16 (Box Box 399)
      - Federal Spending, (Governor Price), 1939 January 28 (Box Box 399)
      - Southside Virginia News - Democracy Edition, 1939 February 23 (Box Box 399)
      - Reciprocal taxation of federal and state employees, 1939 February (Box Box 399)
      - Deficit Spending - Harrison, 1939 March 4 (Box Box 399)
      - Reorganization, 1939 March 6 (Box Box 399)
      - Reorganization, 1939 March 8 (Box Box 399)
      - Reorganization, 1939 March 17 (Box Box 399)
      - Deficit Spending - Eccles, 1939 March 23 (Box Box 399)
      - To expand Tobacco Markets, 1939 March 31 (Box Box 399)
      - Exportation of tobacco seed. (Folder empty when processed), 1939 April 10 (Box Box 399)
      - President's letter to Hitler, 1939 April 17 (Box Box 399)
      - Deficit Spending, 1939 May 23 (Box Box 399)
      - Economy in Government, 1939 June 17 (Box Box 399)
      - Release on Sen. Res. 150, 1939 June 24 (Box Box 399)
      - In connection with Judge Hart's statement, 1939 June (Box Box 399)
      - Bill of Rights, 1939 June (Box Box 399)
      - Exportation of tobacco seed, 1939 July 5 (Box Box 399)
      - Secretary Swanson, 1939 July 10 (Box Box 399)
      - Spending - Lending, 1939 July 23 (Box Box 399)
      - Super toll highways, 1939 July 28 (Box Box 399)
      - Roads - Shenandoah National Park Area, 1939 September 19 (Box Box 399)
      - Neutrality, 1939 September 21 (Box Box 399)
      - Neutrality, 1939 October 16 (Box Box 399)
      - Leesburg Civic Clubs - Newspaper release. (Folder empty when processed), 1939 December 14 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper release on Fredericksburg speech, 1940 January 19 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper release on speech at reopening of Norfolk- Portsmouth Bridge, 1940 February 1 (Box Box 399)
      - In regard to Judge Roberts, 1939 February 10 (Box Box 399)
      - Pursuant to Senate Resolution 150, 1940 February 15 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper statement, 1940 February 20 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper statement. (Folder empty when processed), 1940 February 22 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1940 February 26 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement - $700,000,000 - credit corporations, 1940 March 6 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement - $700,000,000 - credit corporations, 1940 March 12 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement - Tobacco, 1940 March 13 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1940 March 15 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1940 March 26 (Box Box 399)
      - Tobacco Statement, 1940 April 1 (Box Box 399)
      - Statement on death of Lieutenant Governor Saxon Holt, 1940 April 1 (Box Box 399)
      - Tobacco - seed exportation, 1940 April 2 (Box Box 399)
      - Tobacco Res. Statement, 1940 April 10 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement. Re: President's letter on $700,000,000, 1940 April 22 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement - Defense, 1940 May 15 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1940 May 16 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1940 May 21 (Box Box 399)
      - "5th. Column", 1940 May 23 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement - Senator Byrd's speech in regard to J. Edgar Hoover, 1940 May 31 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement - President's l0% reduction, 1940 June 3 (Box Box 399)
      - Tobacco Statement, (seed bill passed and law), 1940 June 7 (Box Box 399)
      - Congress should remain in session, 1940 June 7 (Box Box 399)
      - National Defense and Reduction in appropriations, 1940 June 10 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement, re: Senator Byrd's speech - Forum. (Folder empty when processed), 1940 June 11 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement - Alien Bill, 1940 June 18 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement - Tobacco Tax, 1940 June 18 (Box Box 399)
      - Death of Hon. J. Murray Hooker, 1940 August 7 (Box Box 399)
      - With respect to Camp Lee, 1940 August 14 (Box Box 399)
      - Conscription Statement, 1940 August 21 (Box Box 399)
      - National Defense Contracts, 1940 August 25 (Box Box 399)
      - Statement and Resolution to create a Congressional National Defense Council, 1940 August 26 (Box Box 399)
      - National Defense Contracts, 1940 August 27 (Box Box 399)
      - Pending Tax Bill, 1940 September 14 (Box Box 399)
      - Statement on Adjourning, 1940 September 25 (Box Box 399)
      - Taxation, 1940 September 30 (Box Box 399)
      - Tobacco Statement, 1940 October 7 (Box Box 399)
      - Payments to Sugar Producers. (not released), 1940 October 9 (Box Box 399)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1940 November 8 (Box Box 399)
      - Appointment of William S. Knudsen, 1940 December 22 (Box Box 399)
      - Statement - Budget Message, 1941 January 8 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement - Death of Jim Barron, 1941 January 13 (Box Box 400)
      - Taxation of future issues of Federal bonds and notes, 1941 February 21 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1941 February 28 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1941 March 2 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement - Byrd Amendment - Lend-Lease Bill, 1941 March 5 (Box Box 400)
      - Letter to Secretary Wickard regarding Sugar payments, 1941 March 6 (Box Box 400)
      - Strikes, 1941 March 19 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement - Liquor, Army Camps, 1941 March 21 (Box Box 400)
      - Argentine beef, 1941 March 21 (Box Box 400)
      - U. S. News - Strikes, 1941 April 1 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement - Strikes, 1941 April 3 (Box Box 400)
      - Statement on behalf of the Rules Committee, 1941 April 29 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1941 May 8 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1941 May 26 (Box Box 400)
      - Statement to Jack Bell, 1941 June 6 (Box Box 400)
      - National Defense - Strikes, 1941 June 7 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement - Strike Resolution, 1941 June 9 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement - Strike Resolution, 1941 June 13 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement - Hudson Cary, 1941 July 26 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement, 1941 August 19 (Box Box 400)
      - Reply to President Roosevelt. "Wisecracking has its place, etc.", 1941 August 22 (Box Box 400)
      - Aid to Great Britain, 1941 August 26 (Box Box 400)
      - Statement with Resolution and Amendment, 1941 August 28 (Box Box 400)
      - Regarding tax on tobacco, 1941 August 29 (Box Box 400)
      - Re: Baruch Statement, 1941 September 5 (Box Box 400)
      - Statement of Dr. James Truslow Adams regarding Senator's Amendment, 1941 September 12 (Box Box 400)
      - Rep. Smith's Statement, Re: Arlington, Alexandria and Fairfax Community Chests. Note: Senator Byrd concurred, 1941 October 23 (Box Box 400)
      - Press Statement: Byrd Speech, Tidewater Wholesale Grocery Association, Virginia Beach, Virginia. (Not used due to vote on Lend Lease Bill.) (Folder empty when processed.), 1941 October 23 (Box Box 400)
      - Strikes, 1941 October 27 (Box Box 400)
      - Statement - Committee to investigate non-essential federal expenditures, 1941 October 29 (Box Box 400)
      - Byrd replies to Press re: John L. Lewis, 1941 November 6 (Box Box 400)
      - Regarding the price of beef cattle, 1941 November 25 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement - Senator Adams death, 1941 December 1 (Box Box 400)
      - Regarding Cong. Smith's labor bill, 1941 December 4 (Box Box 400)
      - Letter to Senator Elbert D. Thomas requesting action on the Smith labor bill, 1941 December 6 (Box Box 400)
      - Statement for International News Service Syndicated Column, 1942 January 2 (Box Box 400)
      - "Why Prudent Spending Will Strengthen Nation In War and Peace." (Folder empty when processed.), 1942 January 2 (Box Box 400)
      - Analysis of Budget as compared to Committee Report, 1942 January 8 (Box Box 400)
      - Statement by Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Expenditures, Senator Byrd, Chairman, 1942 January 23 (Box Box 400)
      - Pensions for Senators and Congressmen, 1942 February 6 (Box Box 400)
      - Letter to Secretary Stimson re: Blackstone, Virginia military camp, 1942 February 12 (Box Box 400)
      - Pension Bill - Detroit News, 1942 February 13 (Box Box 400)
      - Regarding labor problems at Camp Pickett, Blackstone, Virginia, 1942 February 17 (Box Box 400)
      - Regarding the Civil Service Committee and pensions for Senators and Congressmen, 1942 February 19 (Box Box 400)
      - Regarding Dean Landis' appearance before Committee, 1942 February 24 (Box Box 400)
      - Letter to J. E. Barnes, Todd Shipyard Corp., 1942 February 28 (Box Box 400)
      - Letter to Hon. James M. Landis, Director, The Office of Civilian Defense, 1942 March 9 (Box Box 400)
      - Letter to Hon. James M. Landis, Director, The Office of Civilian Defense, in response to his letter of same date, 1942 March 10 (Box Box 400)
      - On the Office of Civilian Defense, 1942 March 12 (Box Box 400)
      - On the Office of Civilian Defense, 1942 March 13 (Box Box 400)
      - Transcript of Senator's testimony before Senate Committee on Education and Labor, 1942 March 24 (Box Box 400)
      - On death of William E. Carson, 1942 March 26 (Box Box 400)
      - Suggestions for Economy - Given to the Baltimore Sun, 1942 March (Box Box 400)
      - Letter to Paul V. McNutt in connection with the Office of Civilian Defense, 1942 April 1 (Box Box 400)
      - Regarding labor situation at Blackstone, Virginia. Information from Mr. John J. Corson, 1942 April 14 (Box Box 400)
      - Regarding "slowdowns" in vital naval production. (Folder empty when processed), 1942 April 14 (Box Box 400)
      - Newspaper Statement - U. S. Employment Service figures, 1942 April 27 (Box Box 400)
      - Senator's reply to Lowell Mellett, 1942 May 2 (Box Box 400)
      - Reprint from news release of the North American Newspaper Alliance by Byrd, re: nonwar, nonessestial spending, 1942 June 6 (Box Box 400)
      - Release - Sugar Situation, 1942 June 8 (Box Box 400)
      - Re: Inflation, 1942 July 16 (Box Box 400)
      - Statement on sugar for canning purposes, 1942 July 31 (Box Box 400)
      - Re: Nation-wide rationing of gasoline, 1942 August 16 (Box Box 400)
      - Re: Treasury plan to tax "Spending", 1942 September 3 (Box Box 400)
      - Re: Rubber, 1942 September 12 (Box Box 400)
      - Re: Paying Virginia State Debt, 1942 September 28 (Box Box 400)
      - Re: Farm Labor Situation, 1942 October 23 (Box Box 400)
      - Statement on Manpower, 1942 November 16 (Box Box 400)
      - Re: Federal employees engaged in actual war construction work, etc., 1942 December 9 (Box Box 400)
      - Re: Economy and the new budget, 1942 December 31 (Box Box 400)
      - Re: Purchase of Stevens Hotel, 1943 January 5 (Box Box 401)
      - Edward J. Flynn Nomination, 1943 January 30 (Box Box 401)
      - Re: Availability of farmers bulletins, 1943 February 17 (Box Box 401)
      - Committee's Report on Questionnaires, 1943 February 17 (Box Box 401)
      - National Resources Planning Board in reply to the President, 1943 February 19 (Box Box 401)
      - Strikes. (Boeing Plant, Seattle and others), 1943 February 28 (Box Box 401)
      - On acquisition and use of motor vehicles by various agencies of the government, 1943 March 5 (Box Box 401)
      - Letter to Secretary Wickard on farm labor and machinery situation, 1943 March 8 (Box Box 401)
      - Statement on Civil Service, 1943 March 10 (Box Box 401)
      - John L. Lewis, 1943 May 4 (Box Box 401)
      - Re: Legislation to negotiate trade agreements with other countries, 1943 May 11 (Box Box 401)
      - War Labor Board - Request for information as to decisions made by the Board, 1943 May 20 (Box Box 401)
      - Additional Report of the CommitteeTravel and Communications in the Federal Government - No. 57, 1943 May 27 (Box Box 401)
      - Subsidy Payments, 1943 May 30 (Box Box 401)
      - Strikes, 1943 June 2 (Box Box 401)
      - Joint Committee Report on Federal Personnel, 1943 June 17 (Box Box 401)
      - Food Subsidies - Letter from Albert S. Goss, Master, The National Grange, 1943 July 3 (Box Box 401)
      - On Manpower and Federal Employees, 1943 September 28 (Box Box 401)
      - Strikes and John L. Lewis, 1943 November 4 (Box Box 401)
      - Secretary Hull, 1943 November 10 (Box Box 401)
      - Outline of Federal Real Estate Report Joint Committee, 1943 November 18 (Box Box 401)
      - Federal Personnel, Additional Report, 1943 November 22 (Box Box 401)
      - Reduction of Nonessestial Federal Expenditures, 1943 December 20 (Box Box 401)
      - Revocation of Esquire's second-class mailing permit, 1943 December 31 (Box Box 401)
      - Penalty Mail Report, 1944 January 21 (Box Box 401)
      - Senator's letter to Hon. Guy Mason, Commissioner, District of Columbia, 1944 January 28 (Box Box 401)
      - Senator's endorsement of message to General Assembly by Governor Darden, 1944 February 1 (Box Box 401)
      - Statement by Senator re: appointment of Senator O' Mahoney as Chairmen of the Democratic Senatorial Committee, 1944 February 3 (Box Box 401)
      - Subsidies, 1944 February 14 (Box Box 401)
      - Veto Message of the President, 1944 February 22 (Box Box 401)
      - Statement on death of Senator Weaver, 1944 March 11 (Box Box 401)